A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Audiovisual Materials, RG 7 FA1801
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Video Recordings, 1986-2007; 3; 2.19 Cubic Feet 5 card file boxes
  - Video History of Alvah Chapman - Part 1, 2004 December 22; Betacam (Box T6)
    Interview with Alvah Chapman, former Knight Foundation trustee. Chapman was interviewed by Hodding Carter (off camera). The interview concentrated on Chapmans experiences at Knight Foundation, Miami Herald, and the Knight brothers. There was no transcript made of the interview.
  - Video History of Alvah Chapman - Part 2, 2004 December 22; Betacam (Box T6)
  - To the Contrary: Ethnic Media Explosion, 2003; VHS (Box T6)
    Knight File Number - 3315
    PBS' To The Contrary. Documentary is "Ethnic Media Explosion" and was produced by Persephone Productions. Produced and distributed with a grant from the Knight Foundation.
  - To the Contrary: Status of Women in the Media, 2003; VHS (Box T6)
    Knight File Number - 3316
    One videotape, of PBS' To The Contrary. Documentary is "Status of Women in the Media" and was produced by Persephone Productions. Produced and distributed with a grant from the Knight Foundation.
  - Zaha Hadid Interview, 2006 October; Digital Betcam (Box T6)
    Knight File Number - 4516
    Videotaped interview of architect Zaha Hadid, who was honored at a luncheon in Miami sponsored by KF.
  - Continental Harmony: Celebrating America Through Music, 2001; VHS (Box T6)
    Knight File Number - 3837
    One videotape, of a PBS documentary, "Continental Harmony", which was sponsored by The Knight Foundation.
  - World Press Institute Roundtable Discussion - Tape A-1, 2003 October 7; VHS (Box T6)
    Knight File Number - 2689
    Roundtable discussion opens with introductory remarks by Hodding Carter on America's response to attack and infringement on civil liberties. Eric Newton then described the Knight Foundation's Journalism program. Fellows, from the countries of Argentina, Cameroon, China, Finland, Germany, India, Romania, Turkey and Zimbabwe, then were free to ask questions of Knight staff or comment on the situation in their respective countries. Participants: Teresa Bausili (La Nacion, Argentina), Bertrand Tchoumi (TBC Radio, Cameroon), Jinmei Lu (Shanghai Broadcasting Network, China), Kaius Niemi (Helsingin Sanomat, Finland), Lars VonTorne (Der Tagesspiegel, Germany), Shujaat Bukhari (The Hindu, India), Oliver-Tamas Kiss (Szabadsag, Romania), Nevin Sungur (NTV, Turkey), Patience Rusere (The Chronicle, Zimbabwe).
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    The audio-portion is poor; many participants are difficult to hear.
  - World Press Institute Roundtable Discussion - Tape A-2, 2003 October 7; VHS (Box T6)
  - World Press Institute Roundtable Discussion - Tape A-3, 2003 October 7; VHS (Box T6)
  - World Press Institute Roundtable Discussion - Tape A-4, 2003 October 7; VHS (Box T6)
  - Newsleaders: Knight-Ridder, 1986; VHS; 22 minutes (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 5043
    Copy of a news program produced by the Poynter Institute for Media Studies in 1986 on the Knight-Ridder Company and hosted by John Chancellor. It provides some history of the company and features interviews with James L. Knight, Alvah Chapman, and Jim Batten. The Knight Foundation is mentioned as a large shareholder of Knight-Ridder. Much of the emphasis is on the impact of public vs. private ownership of newspapers. Also mentioned is the launch of Gannett's USA TODAY and its impact on the newspaper business. Jim Knight closes the program with the quote: "Change is coming. I hope its minor." This was probably one of the last interviews JLK gave.
  - National Community Development Initiative: An Investment That Works, 1997 June; VHS (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4780
    Videotape highlights the revitalization of Washington, DC's 14th Street Corridor as an example of the work NCDI does. KF is mentioned in end credits.
  - Link TV: Knight Foundation Electronic and New Media Partners, 2004; VHS (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4783
    Tape of the Knight Foundation promotion produced by Link TV features clips of Hodding Carter, Bill Moyers, The Kalb Report, Geneva Overholser, Dan Rather, and Sandra Mims Rowe.
  - Knight Foundation Grant to Benefit Children in Wichita, KS, 2003 November 8; VHS (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4785
    Clips of television coverage of the $1.3 million grant.
  - ICFJ - Andrew Cohen Interviews Hodding Carter, 2004; MiniDV (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4786
    Two mini-cam copies.
  - Penny McPhee Farewell Party - Part 1, 2004; MiniDV (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4787
    Features a duet by Eric Newton and Lynne Noble singing Eric's song: "Get Your Kicks with Knight's 26".
  - Penny McPhee Farewell Party - Part 2, 2004; MiniDV (Box T7)
  - United Agenda for Children Town Hall Meeting, Charlotte, NC, 2004 December 10 (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4788
    Clips from television news broadcasts re: 40 organizations who sponsored a United Agenda for Children town meeting, attended by about 1500 people. One vhs tape and one mini-dvd tape.
  - Hodding Carter Clips, c. 2004; Betacam (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4789
  - Knight Program in Community Building, c. 1999 (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4782
    Videotape of lecture at the University of Miami School of Architecture which featured a conversation in community building with Hodding Carter and Donna Shalala. Two copies: one vhs and one mini-beta cam.
  - Overtown: The Villages of St. Agnes, 1998; VHS (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4781
    Videotape highlights the revitalization of a section of Miami's Overtown neighborhood. Made for the Collins Center.
  - Hodding Carter Keynote Address, 2004 April 24; VHS (Box T7)
    Knight File Number - 4784
    Tape of Hodding Carter's speech at the Civil Rights and the Press Symposium at the Newhouse School, Syracuse University. Carter used his family's history to put the civil rights struggle into context.
    Note: Carter is obscured at times by people walking in front of the camera.
- Microfiche, 1950-1994; 4; 2.78 Cubic Feet 5 card file boxes
  - Administrative Files, 1952-1994; 1; 0.31 Cubic Feet 1 card file box
    Administrative Files on Microfiche contain 292 fiche. They include records from 10 record groups, dating from 1952-1994.
    - Administrative Files on Microfiche, 1952-1994 (Box 1)
      Knight File Number - 971
  - Grant Files, 1950-1994; 2; 2.47 Cubic Feet 8 card file boxes
    Grant Files on Microfiche contain documentation for 2,627 grants. The microfiche are filed alphabetically by organization name. A report, prepared in 1997, lists organization name and number, grant number, date grant approved, and amount granted.
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (A-B), 1950-1994 (Box 1)
      Knight File Number - 2493
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (C-Detroit Historical Society), 1950-1994 (Box 2)
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (D-Handicapped Organized Women, Inc.), 1950-1994 (Box 3)
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (H continued-Mana Sota), 1950-1994 (Box 4)
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (M continued-Northwest), 1950-1994 (Box 5)
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (O-Samaritans), 1950-1994 (Box 6)
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (S continued-United States), 1950-1994 (Box 7)
    - Grant Files on Microfiche (U continued-Zorongo), 1950-1994 (Box 8)
- Photographs, 1890-2019; 5; 5.08 Cubic Feet 12 containers
  - Commissions and Task Forces, 1992-2001; 1; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1991-1994 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Knight File Number - 944
      Photographs of members of the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics at meetings. Includes photos of Creed Black, Reverend Theodore Hesburgh, and Bill Friday. Black & white.
    - Kids Voting Program, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Knight File Number - 855
    - Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Knight File Number - 870
      Negative and transparencies of photos taken of the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics for the 1993 Annual Report, page 83. Black & white.
    - Knight Commission Meeting, 2000 August 28 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Knight File Number - 4435
      Contact sheets and negatives, and some photographs in b&w and color, of the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics meeting in Washington, DC. Photos are by Lisa Helfert.
    - Knight Commission Meeting, 2000 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Knight File Number - 4436
      Contact sheets and negatives of a Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics meeting in Washington, DC. Photos are by Lisa Helfert.
    - Knight Commission Meeting, 2000 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Knight File Number - 4437
      Contact sheets and negatives and some photographs, of a Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics meeting in Washington, DC. Photos are by Lisa Helfert.
    - Knight Commission Press Conference, 2001 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Knight File Number - 4438
      Contact sheets and negatives, and some color photographs, of a Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics press conference in Washington, DC. Photos are by Lisa Helfert.
    - Knight Commission Press Conference, 2001 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Knight File Number - 4439
      Contact sheets and negatives, of a Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics press conference in Washington, DC. Photos are by Lisa Helfert.
  - Events, 1993-2012; 2; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1993 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Knight File Number - 860
      Photographs of the Board of Trustees meeting in Detroit in June 1993. Includes photos of Jim Batten, Lee Hills and group photos of the trustees (Jill Conway, Alvah Chapman, Creed Black, Gerald Austen, Jim Spaniolo, C.C. Gibson, and Beverly Knight Olson).
    - John S. Knight Center, 1994 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Knight File Number - 871
      Photograph of the John S. Knight Center in Akron, OH, on the day of its dedication, 6/21/94. Color.
    - Arts Award Ceremony with Penny McPhee, 1995 April (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Knight File Number - 2525
      One photo, b&w, showing Penny McPhee holding an award with Sandra Mortham. Joe Reiter looks on.
    - Kids Voting Kentucky, 1995 July 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Knight File Number - 2526
      Three photos, color, of a Fourth of July parade in Lexington, Kentucky, featuring 125 people marching for Kids Voting Kentucky.
    - Lee Hills Hall Dedication, 1995 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
      Knight File Number - 882
      Photographs and negatives of the Dedication of Lee Hills Hall at the University of Missouri-Columbia School of Journalism. 2 folders. Black & white and color.
    - Staff/Board of Trustees Site Visit to Independence Hall, Philadelphia, PA, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Knight File Number - 2400
      Four photos (two b/w, two color) showing Knight Foundation staff and trustees entering and inside Independence Hall, Pbiladelphia, PA.
    - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Knight File Number - 2469
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at: Baby Shower for Stacey Campbell Cape Florida Volunteer Project Day Kay Simpson/Robb Kevers Football rivalry Decorating Office for the Holidays Corporate Run Color
    - Board of Trustees Meeting - San Jose, 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Knight File Number - 5871
      Six b/w photographs of the Board of Trustees meeting in San Jose in June 1997. Includes photos of Lee Hills, Alvah Chapman, Creed Black, Tom Johnson, Gerald Austen, Marjorie Crane, and Beverly Knight Olson. Includes a site visit to the San Jose Museum of Art Association.
    - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Knight File Number - 2470
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at: Kay Simpson/Robb Kevers Football Rivalry (continued) Corporate Run Corporate Volunteer Day Janice Howard Wedding Shower Creed Black as a "prisoner" to raise money for charity Color
    - Board of Trustees Site Visit - Grand Forks, ND, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Knight File Number - 5872
      Visit by KF Trustees and Staff to Grand Forks, ND, one year after the devastating flood and fire. Included a community dinner.
    - Creed Black Retirement Dinner, 1998 May (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Knight File Number - 2537
      Six color photos and three contact sheets of Creed Black's retirement dinner. Photos include Alvah Chapman, Gerry Austen, Jill Conway, Sr. Jeanne, Lee Hills, Jim Spaniolo, Beverly Olson, and Marjorie Crane.
    - Dedication of the Homeless Assistance Center (HAC), Miami, 1998 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Knight File Number - 4580
      Nine color photos of the Dedication, featuring Alvah Chapman, who spoke, Mayor Alex Penelas and Creed Black.
    - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Knight File Number - 2471
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at: Records Clean Out Day Corporate Run Creed Black Retirement Holiday Party Color
    - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Knight File Number - 2473
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at: Baby Shower for George Martinez Farewell Breakfast for Jennifer Dakroub Records Clean Out Day Corporate Run Mini Golf Outing Family Fun Day at Arcade Halloween Party Holiday Party Color
    - Board of Trustees Meeting in Macon and Milledgeville, GA, 1999 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Knight File Number - 5876
      Color and b/w photographs of the meetings and reception, which included KF staff and community leaders.
    - Presidential Leadership/Board of Trustees Reception, 1999 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Knight File Number - 2401
      Six color photographs of the reception, which included Knight Foundation trustees and college presidents.
    - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Knight File Number - 2474
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at: Records Clean Out Day 50th Anniversary Family Day at Miami Metro Zoo Color; 2 folders
    - Board of Trustees Meeting - Akron, 2000 June (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Knight File Number - 5873
      Color photos of event, featuring a reception, and tour.
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Long Beach, CA Day Care Center, 2002 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Knight File Number - 4581
      Thumbnails and cd of event with children and trustees.
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Long Beach, CA Day Care Center - J.E. Flores photos (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - KF Holiday Party, 2002 December (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Knight File Number - 5603
      Candid photographs (color) of the KF staff holiday party, which featured a boat cruise and dancing.
    - Family Day Bowling Party, 2003 January (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Knight File Number - 5878
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at a Miami bowling alley. Color
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Bradenton, FL Early Childhood Education Program, 2003 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Knight File Number - 4582
      Thumbnails and cd of event with children, parents and trustees.
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Bradenton, FL Early Childhood Education Program - Harllee Middle School photos (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Family Day at the Beach, 2003 March 24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Knight File Number - 5880
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at a Miami area beach. Color
    - Knight Chairs and Knight Mid-Career Journalism Directors Meet During AEJMC Meeting, 2003 July 29 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Knight File Number - 4584
      Thumbnails and cds of meeting.
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Columbus, GA, Mildred L. Terry Library and Community Meeting, 2003 June 9-10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Knight File Number - 4583
      Photographs, thumbnails and cds of event with children, and trustees.
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Columbus, GA, Mildred L. Terry Library and Community Meeting - Disk 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Columbus, GA, Mildred L. Terry Library and Community Meeting - Disk 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Akron, OH CAC Meeting at the University of Akron, 2003 November 5 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Knight File Number - 4585
    - Akron, OH CAC Meeting at the University of Akron - Edits and Outakes by Bruce Zake (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Grants Review Committee Meeting in Lexington, KY with Arnold Gaither, 2004 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Knight File Number - 4586
    - Grants Review Committee Meeting in Lexington, KY with Arnold Gaither - File Disc, 2004 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Grants Review Committee Meeting in Lexington, KY with Arnold Gaither - Edited Disc, 2004 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Family Day Rodeo, 2004 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Knight File Number - 5879
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at a Miami area rodeo. Included hay rides and petting zoo. Color
    - Civil Rights and The Press Conference, Syracuse University, with Hodding Carter, 2004 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Knight File Number - 4588
      Thumbnails and 3 cds of meeting.
    - Civil Rights and The Press Conference, Syracuse University, with Hodding Carter - Keynote Address (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights and The Press Conference, Syracuse University, with Hodding Carter - Saturday and Sunday Photos by Alexander Koromilas (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights and The Press Conference, Syracuse University, with Hodding Carter - Friday Reception Photos by Alexander Koromilas (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Neiman Foundation Opens Knight Wing at Harvard University, 2004 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Knight File Number - 4589
      Thumbnails and cd of meeting which included remarks by Hodding Carter. Knight Foundation staff and trustees were in attendance.
    - Neiman Foundation Opens Knight Wing at Harvard University - Pam Berry Photos (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - KF Trustees - Bus Tour of Camden, NJ and National Constitution Center, 2004 June 14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Knight File Number - 4590
      Thumbnails and 2 cds of tour and reception which included remarks by Hodding Carter and Jerry Austen. Knight Foundation staff and trustees were in attendance.
    - KF Trustees - Bus Tour of Camden, NJ and National Constitution Center - JPEG Images Disk 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - KF Trustees - Bus Tour of Camden, NJ and National Constitution Center - JPEG Images Disk 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Detroit YMCA Press Conference, 2004 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Knight File Number - 4591
      Thumbnails and 2 cds of press conference featuring Detroit Mayor Kwame Kilpatrick, Mike Maidenberg, Joe Ervin, Brenda Price and Geneva Williams, Chair, KF Detroit Community Advisory Committee.
    - Detroit YMCA Press Conference - Fabrizio(?) Constantim disk 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Detroit YMCA Press Conference - Fabrizio(?) Constantim disk 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Detroit YMCA Press Conference - Fabrizio(?) Constantim disk 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Jill Conway Retirement Dinner, 2004 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Knight File Number - 4592
      Trustee dinner in honor of retiring Vice Chair, Jill Ker Conway. Photos, negatives, and cds with trustees, spouses, guests and retired trustees.
    - Jill Conway Retirement Dinner - Jill Conway and W. Gerald Austen by Harvey Bilt (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Jill Conway Retirement Dinner - Walgreens Picture CD (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Fund for Our Economic Future Meeting, Akron, OH with Rob Briggs, 2005 March (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Knight File Number - 4587
      Thumbnails and cd of meeting.
    - Fund for Our Economic Future Meeting, Akron, OH with Rob Briggs - Edits and Outtakes (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Joe Ervin and Lisa Versaci Goodbye Party, 2005 May 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Knight File Number - 4560
      Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff at the going away party for Joe Ervin and Lisa Versaci. Digital color photos on cd.
    - Joe Ervin and Lisa Versaci Goodbye Party - Photos by R. Adams (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Charlotte, NC, 2005 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Knight File Number - 4561
      Board of trustees meeting and Charlotte Crossroads conference. Digital color photos on cd and color photos of conference attendees, trustees and staff.
    - Board of Trustees Visit to Charlotte, NC - Project and Dinner (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Hodding Carter Retirement Party, 2005 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Knight File Number - 4562
      Staff party for Hodding at Books and Books. Informal digital photographs and video (4 cds).
    - Hodding Carter Retirement Party - Video by Robbie Adams (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Hodding Carter Retirement Party - Photos by Robbie Adams (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Alberto Ibarguen and Mike Maidenberg View Biloxi Storm Damage, 2005 September 4 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Knight File Number - 4593
      Alberto and Mike rushed to the scene of some of the worst devastation caused by Hurricane Katrina and viewed the damage with Ricky Mathews of the Sun Herald.
    - Hodding Carter Retirement Dinner, 2005 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Knight File Number - 4564
      Trustee dinner for Hodding at Gusman Center for the Performing Arts in downtown Miami. Digital photographs on 2 cds. Features staff, trustees, spouses and friends.
    - Hodding Carter Retirement Dinner - Tribute at Gusman by H. Bilt Disk 1, 2005 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hodding Carter Retirement Dinner - Tribute at Gusman by H. Bilt Disk 2, 2005 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Voices and Choices Town Hall Meeting, Akron, OH, 2005 December 16 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Knight File Number - 4563
      Town Hall Meeting features Rob Briggs, KF trustee.
    - Voices and Choices Town Hall Meeting, Akron, OH - Edits and Panoramics (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Miami Performing Arts Center Trustee Tour and Press Conference, 2006 July 19 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Knight File Number - 4565
      Trustee and staff tour of the KF-sponsored Miami Performing Arts Center under construction. Also includes photos of a press conference, featuring Alberto Ibarguen.
    - Miami Performing Arts Center Trustee Tour and Press Conference - MPAC by Robin Hill, 2006 July 19 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - KF Holiday Party at the Ibarguens, 2007 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Knight File Number - 4566
      Informal photos of staff enjoying the holiday party, which featured a mariachi band. Digital color photos on cd.
    - KF Holiday Party at the Ibarguens (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - KF Staff working with Habitat for Humanity, Biloxi, MS, 2008 May 11-16 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Knight File Number - 4567
      KF staffers spent a week helping to build a house in Hurricane Katrina-devastated Biloxi, MS, with Habitate for Humanity. Informal color photos on cd.
    - KF Staff working with Habitat for Humanity, Biloxi, MS - Biloxi by Tom Pitman (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Ceremony Honoring W. Gerald Austen, Akron, OH, 2009 September 9 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Knight File Number - 4594
      Ceremony and reception honoring Jerry Austen, retiring Chair of KF. Includes announcement of the naming of the Austen BioInnovation Institute. The other KF trustees and Austen family were in attendance. Includes 2 sets of thumbnails and 2 sets of 3 cds.
    - Ceremony Honoring W. Gerald Austen, Akron, OH - High Res Photos Disk 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Ceremony Honoring W. Gerald Austen, Akron, OH - High Res Photos Disk 2 (Box 3, Folder 11)